question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The bikini is named after the &quot;Bikini Atoll&quot;, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr. and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Santa Claus&quot; is a variety of melon.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "Francis Bacon died from a fatal case of pneumonia while he was attempting to preserve meat by stuffing a chicken with snow.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
